[Music]
thank you for calling internet services
this is chalene help me help you today
this is linda our internet stops in
stein and i have an online closet too so
i need this internet fix right now
well thank you for letting us know about
this immediately linda so i can help you
get back online
may have the phone number associated
with your internet service
the phone number is 855-3232
thank you so that's
855-3232 correct
and can you confirm the name of the
account please
it's linda bloom it's me
thanks so much you're welcome
linda are you near to your modem right
now yes i'm sitting next to it what do
you want me to do
okay great
first we'll go ahead and check the
lights on your modem can you please tell
me which lights are on right now
the lights look normal as if the service
is working
thank you
that sounds interesting
let me run a quick line check to confirm
the modem's connectivity okay
okay
linda any chance that you guys
experience any power flagged wave shane
sort of thing
no
any power outage just recently
all right thank you for confirming that
uh
i just got the results here and the
modem shows it has connection from our
end going into that modem that's why it
has the normal lights as if it's working
now let's try to check and make sure
that this modem indeed is getting the
internet service
okay what do you want me to do
uh linda let me just confirm this
the computer that you're using to access
the internet isn't connected through
wi-fi or it's white directly to the back
of your modem router it's a desktop
computer so it's wired
i see thank you uh would i also want to
know if you have other devices in your
house right now that's connected to your
home internet i do i have two phones in
a laptop
are they not getting online too yeah all
of them can't go online there's no
internet service
i see have you tried to reboot your
modem router earlier no i want to give
you guys a call first i don't want to
cause any trouble
okay cool at this time window i'll be
needing your help to check the physical
connection like the cable from the back
of a modem router going to the computer
that you're using just to make sure that
both ends are snug fit and not loose
okay
all right uh hold on let me check
yeah uh both ends are properly connected
not loose great thank you uh linda we're
almost done
now we'll go ahead and reboot your modem
router you just need to unplug it from
power and once unplugged we'll just need
to wait for 20 or 30 seconds and then
plug it back in okay
all right
it's off now
okay good
we'll just wait for 30 seconds
okay
it's a tough job though
yeah sometimes it's challenging
i enjoy doing it though
that's nice
[Music]
all right i guess uh 30 seconds it
passed so you can turn it back on now
then we'll wait until the normal lights
come back then after that we'll check if
we have internet connectivity okay
sure
well
uh the the lights are coming on now
and i think
the
the internet is back
i'm getting bunch of emails now
great
wait uh holland let me check my pc
yeah sure
all right
my computer is also working
great
so
i think we're good thanks so much for
your help julian
by the way
is it necessary to do this once in a
while yes you can do it every once in a
while anyways uh electronic devices are
not built to constantly be running at
all times and power recycle really helps
because when you leave your modem on for
too long it will tend to stop performing
at its best after a while so rebooting
your modem can affect the the internet
connection problems it improves slow
moving connections and resolve wireless
issues too which also affect your
digital tv service or video streaming
services like
netflix or
amazon tv or apple tv that's being
transmitted over the internet connection
so by unplugging the power cord from the
back of the modem or your router you're
giving it the breather it needs
oh
i see well thanks for letting me know i
never thought of that email's welcome
linda i'm so glad that i was able to
help you get back online and remove this
of your word list today so you can just
focus on your online class later at 2.
absolutely
oh dear
you saved my day and you made my day
linda thanks for partnering with me
is there anything else i could further
assist you with no you've covered
everything i need all right then thanks
so much for choosing internet services
bye
[Music]